http://www.guitarsite.com/privacy/

Skip to Navigation
Privacy Policy
GuitarSite.com, and its publisher Hitsquad Pty Ltd, values Your privacy.
Personal Information
We collect personal information about our users during registration for paid services and some free services, from our use of "cookie" technology as you use the service and sometimes during entry into a contest or sweepstakes.
We uses reasonable precautions to keep any personal information disclosed to us secure and we never disclose such information to third parties without your express permission. We only ever use personal information for the exact purpose we stated when you gave it to us. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. We also link to a wide variety of other sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.
Our Use Of Cookies
We primarily only set 'session cookies' which disappear from your browser when you close it down, although we may occasionally set longer lasting cookies for registered members. Only we can retrieve the cookies we have set in your browser - no other web site can see this information.
We use cookies to maintain virtual 'sessions' for your web browser so that our web server knows which information to display to you when it has to make a choice. This might be to decide if you are allowed to view certain information (such as our paid Membership service) or it may be to decide which sponsor's message or advertisement to show you.
Aggregated Information
We also collect aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to visitors' needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. Because GuitarSite.com derives its revenue mainly from advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users.
Third Party Advertising
GuitarSite.com uses the services of third party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit.
These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to these and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here click here.
Third Party Cookies
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
More Information About Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of information that may be placed into your browser by any web server your browser connects to. Cookies can only be retrieved by a web server from the same domain name as the one that placed it there. You can change the way your browser handles cookies, or disable them completely by changing your browser's preferences. You can do this under the Tools>Internet Options menu in Microsoft Internet Explorer, see your Help menu in other browsers for information on how to do this.
Amazon
GutarSite.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com, Amazon.ca, Amazon.co.uk and other Amazon stores worldwide.
Amazon may also set cookies when you click on advertising links to visit their websites.
Contact GuitarSite.com / Hitsquad Pty Ltd
Please contact us for more information about our privacy policy if required.
This site is published by Hitsquad Pty Ltd.
Copyright © 1999 - 2020 , All Rights Reserved.
Affiliate Notice: As an Amazon Associate we earn from qualifying purchases.
